Osvaldo Salomon-Vazquez

I'm a creative and skilled software developer. My expertise lies in problem-solving, communication, and collaboration, supported by a solid background in front-end and web app development. With experience in industries such as Home & Personal Care and Customer Experience, I have successfully contributed to various projects, including the development of intuitive user interfaces, reusable components, and fixing of critical bugs.

Atlanta, GA (404) 429-4388 osvaldosalomonv@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Accenture, Atlanta, GA—Software Developer

AUGUST 2023 - PRESENT

NADA (Not Another Dating App), Atlanta, GA —Software Developer Intern

MARCH 2023 - AUGUST 2023

EDUCATION

App Academy Coding Bootcamp, Remote — Full Stack Web Development

FEBRUARY 2022 - AUGUST 2022

Coding boot camp prioritizing the fundamentals of web development. One of the top-ranked software engineering boot camps in the country with a < 3% acceptance rate and over 1000 hours of instruction and pair programming.

PROIECTS

Project MARS— Software Development

Developed and integrated reusable components and features that contributed to the overall app. · Collaborated with designers to implement a responsive and intuitive user interface. · Diagnosed and fixed critical bugs related to navigation and state management, resulting in a smoother user experience and fewer crashes. · Worked closely with a team of developers, designers, and product managers, contributing to daily stand-ups and sprint planning sessions.

Project mAIr (GenAI powered 3D humanoid)— Software Development and Testing

Evaluated Conversation Flow and Implemented Improvements · Assessed and analyzed the conversation flow within the Digital Human Portal to ensure consistency with the Figma design specifications. · Developed a comprehensive testing tracker to systematically document and address identified issues. · Enhanced AWS Lex by adding new intents to resolve identified bugs and improve overall functionality.

Project EA Hub & Capability Uplift — Technical Contribution and Support

Developed and configured connectors for SharePoint and Confluence, facilitating seamless integration with Microsoft Search. • Created detailed PowerPoint presentations on BCM and APO strategies, aiding stakeholder communication and understanding. • Played a crucial role in testing and validating connector functionality and performance to ensure optimal operation. • Produced and updated documentation for the BCM in OrbusInfinity, aligning business capabilities with technological infrastructure.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

JavaScript, Python,
Node.js, React.js, Redux,
Angular, React Native,
Expo, Express.js, Flask,
PostgreSQL, TypeScript,
Sequelize,
SQLAlchemy,Figma,
HTML5, CSS3, Linux, Java,
NPM, REST APIs,
Git/Github, Material UI,
Bootstrap, Next.js, UI / UX

SOFT SKILLS

Communication,
Problem-Solving, Critical
Thinking, Adaptability,
Teamwork, Time
Management, Attention to
Detail, Creativity, Patience,
Ability to Learn Quickly

LANGUAGES

English, Spanish